"At night, a mysterious sound
leaves me unable to sleep.
"There are more stray cats
and dogs now.
"Grandfather went for a walk
and hasn't returned.
"The nearby forest suddenly fell silent.
For a few days now,
the livestock has been afraid of
something and it's causing problems."
And this is where
each of these has occurred.
Wait...
Similar to the incident
in the Forest of Beasts,
if the enemy has already encroached
this deep into our country...
All members who can use
Search and Uncover
will form a group and dispatch
to the areas indicated, now.
And call for all Six Sovereigns,
this is an emergency summons.
All of them?!
Hurry! Do it now!
Yes, sir!
Why did I not
take notice of this earlier?!
What in the world is this?
Those bastards of the Magical Empire,
are they really going this far?!
What the hell did our country
do to them?!
They want the dungeon's resources
so badly they'd resort to this?!
Do they not understand how many
innocent lives are in the line of fire?!
This is... this is just like...
like they're coming to this country
to demolish it!
Good thing we got compensated
in the end, huh?
You got that right.
Good grief,
guess I'll do you a favor then.
What's this?
It's in celebration of your first hunt.
Take it.
Are you sure?
Don't worry about it.
One goblin only gets you
so much anyways.
Food sure tastes better
after finishing our first hunt!
Yeah!
But how long is this girl
going to stick around?
Her folks must be worried about her too.
Thanks for the meal.
Now then, I think I'll head back
to my home for today.
Great!
Is that okay, Instructor?
Yes, of course!
You truly were a big help today.
Oh no, I'll assist you again
if you don't mind me doing so.
So this is where you've been, Lynne.
Brother.
Sir Noor.
I apologize for bringing
this up so suddenly,
but will you head to a city
in the mountain district
tomorrow morning with Lynne?
Huh?
Me?
I'll give you a carriage
as well as one escort.
I'm sorry I'm unable to give you
any more details right now,
but I'd like you to cooperate with us.
I see. Sounds like I'll need
to pack for this journey.
We will pay you well
and cover your travel expenses.
Please.
You are the sole person
I can rely on right now.
We ended up taking his request
through the guild.
Master did say to relax
and go on a long journey
since it's a pretty sweet deal.
But the real reason I accepted
the task this time is...
I've never been on a carriage before,
and I just wanted to see what it's like.
To me, who only knows places
around the capital,
this is the greatest compensation.
Seems like if luck is with me,
I'll be able to go
to other countries, too!
Lynne, don't you wanna see the scenery?
It's just about time
for the wheat harvest.
We sure do live in a land of plenty.
Uh... yeah.
I want to become a normal adventurer
and journey on my own.
I'm so sorry my brother
burdened you with this request.
Don't worry about it.
I'm getting paid for this,
and I owe you for the goblin hunt.
First, you'll travel
northwest of the capital via carriage
heading towards
the mountain district of Toros,
then you two will just sit tight
there for a while.
After that, if nothing especially
abnormal happens,
then you'll cross the mountain
and head towards the neighboring land,
The Holy Theocracy of Mithra.
Is it really okay
that I'm just going along?
Yes, it's something like a trip...
That is, if nothing happens.
I truly hope nothing will happen.
Not to worry.
That is what I'm here for.
Ines...
I received a secret order
from the prince.
In the near future,
the royal capital will fall
into an unprecedented crisis.
Should you receive report of
the destruction of the capital...
At that time,
take Lynne together with Sir Noor,
and flee to The Holy Theocracy of Mithra.
Does Lady Lynneburg know of this?
I haven't told her.
If I had, she'd surely say
she's staying here.
But I can't be away from the capital
if there is an emergency...
This duty of yours
is of the utmost importance.
You are the only one
I can trust Lynne with.
You must bring her somewhere safe.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, Your Highness.
Sir Noor.
I apologize that you're
caught up in this now.
You make a simple trip
sound so serious.
More importantly, you haven't
been looking too well this whole trip.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm just a little worried
about something.
Keeping you safe is another one
of my responsibilities.
You don't need to worry.
Well, I'm not really worried
about anything at all.
I intend to protect myself
as much as possible.
I'm confident I can run away if needed.
You won't need to do that.
I have a shield.
A shield?
Well, it looks you don't have
anything though.
In my case, I don't need
to have anything.
Rather, it's better in
many ways if I have nothing.
It'd be easier to just show you.
Divine Shield.
Whoa...
That's amazing...
This is your shield, then?
Yes.
If anything happens,
hide yourself behind this shield of light.
Neither weapons nor magic can
get through this, for the most part.
I see. I'll do that then.
According to Lynne, that man with
the spear that let me train with him
on the practice drill grounds...
I think it was Gil...
Val? No...
Armadillo!
His talent is so great
he brought down a dragon on his own.
And she is no less powerful than he is.
A single goblin gives me so much trouble.
They're on a whole
different level then I am.
That is a remarkable talent, seriously.
Talent, huh?
I noticed there was
a mysterious power within me...
shortly after being
taken into an orphanage.
Ines, what's that?
It sure is pretty.
Ouch! It hurts!
I'm hurt! Ow!
What's happened?!
Someone! Call Director Sain!
I'm hurt! Ow!
I healed her, so don't worry.
Now, show me the power
you were using.
Hm...
This is a gift from the heavens.
A gift?
What's more,
a historically rare one at that.
It could become a blade
to cut anyone down,
or a shield that can protect
against anything.
Depending on how you use it,
it can easily annihilate even a country.
Ines, was it?
It's all right.
You can learn to use it starting now.
I'm ready!
I was taken in by
the Sovereign Shield Dandalg,
and I learned from the Six Sovereigns
how to use my power.
Even so, I couldn't dispel the fear
that I would hurt someone again.
Naturally, I started to put distance
between myself and others,
and became detached
from the things they said and did.
At least, that's what I'd thought...
May I have your name,
if you don't mind?
I'm Noor.
Noor?
I knew the name of that man.
Never let yourself get distracted.
Dandalg, the foster father who raised me,
and the instructor I held in high regard.
I'm sorry, Father.
He would tell me about any little thing,
and I heard it from him.
Another separate swarm of monsters
He would tell me about any little thing,
and I heard it from him.
are approaching from the west.
It never ends.
The state of affairs
is pretty tough right now.
The soldiers seem to be showing
signs of fatigue.
Times like this...
I wish that Noor was still around.
That name again...
Oops, that slipped out.
Forget I said that.
Noor...
A person worth recognition by Father.
Even though I'm right here...
The emotions that swelled up
inside me were so strange.
It seemed I was somehow still envious
of that man I'd never met before.
It's been even worse since that man
appeared in front of me.
No, I shouldn't let my feelings
cloud my judgment.
I am the Shield of the Clays Kingdom.
I protect Lady Lynneburg with my life.
That is my duty.
What's that?
There's a path in the wheat fields.
It's like someone made it there.
Sir Noor, is there something wrong?
Nah, I thought I saw something
moving in the field.
Stop right here!
Uncover!
So it has begun.
Reporting in!
Several beasts have appeared
all around the royal capital!
The Warrior Corps are handling it,
but we don't have enough soldiers
for the situation!
Have the swordsman troop block the
roads immediately to fend them off
while evacuating the citizens.
Reroute the Secret Corps and the
Hunter Corps to send as many as possible
in order to fight the monsters!
Don't let a single citizen
become a casualty!
Yes, sir!
That damn Deridas...
You'll regret those words!
He's come to make good
on that threat, has he?
I fear this is just the beginning.
I don't believe it will end with this.
I suppose it will not.
And the Sovereign Six?
We've dispatched them all.
Powerful monsters were discovered
in various locations,
and each of them had no choice
but to counter them.
Defend this place at all costs!
Don't let a single one of 'em through!
You mean they've spread
our forces thin?
Yes.
Lynne and the others are safe,
I suspect they've arrived in the city.
I have to kill them...
Could that possibly be...
the Black Death Dragon!
Why is such a vicious monster
in a place like this?!
Wait! That's a-
Parry!
Did you notice?
That boy didn't just happen to be there,
he appeared along
with the Black Death Dragon
when you used your "Uncover" skill.
You mean, that kid is...
Demonfolk?
Yes.
You've heard of them, haven't you?
They appear to be the same as humans,
but they are demi-humans who have
the special ability
of establishing a mental bond
with monsters at will.
If anything, they are closer
to monsters than humans,
and are considered abhorrent.
There are records from 200 years ago,
when the Holy Theocracy of Mithra
was almost wiped out
by demi-humans who were
manipulating powerful monsters.
Because of that the Demonfolk
were exhaustively hunted by humans,
and they were thought to be extinct.
It seems their descendants
are somehow still around.
If that is the case,
then they must hold some
intense hatred towards humans.
Then the boy manipulated
the dragon to come here?
They are monsters
that dwell in the marshlands.
They rarely go where humans reside.
Basically, that boy clearly
intends to try and bring
that vicious monster
to the royal capital.
The shock of being exposed by Uncover
caused him to lose
his mental hold on the dragon.
I can't believe he'd rush to help
someone like that.
It's foolish.
Excessively so.
What in the world is that man doing?
What is he thinking?!
Whatever it is, let's assist him!
Wait right there.
I will not help Sir Noor again.
This frog...
It's not so powerful,
and moves slowly.
That goblin was leagues tougher than this.
If I can hold out until
Lynne and Ines get here,
we'll make it out of here all right.
If I evade it now, the kid'll get hit!
What is this?
Instructor!
That's the true horror of the dragon.
It's poison... a deadly one at that...
My head's spinning...
I can't control my body...
Ines was trying to say something..
Did she want to tell me
that it wasn't a regular frog,
but a poisonous one?!
It brings a black death
to all living things,
thus it is called the
Black Death Dragon.
Instructor Noor!
You mustn't go!
Next an even bigger
poisonous mist will come.
Please, let me go to him!
I can't.
My duty is to protect you!
If I can hold back its attacks
here somehow
so at least the princess escapes...
then there's a chance
to revive the kingdom.
Please understand.
The very existence of the kingdom
is at stake here!
But-
Regardless, one breath of
that noxious gas would be fatal.
Even if the
Sovereign Healer Sain were here,
recovery would be a challenge.
No way...
Here it comes!
Quick, get behind me!
For now, you just need to survive!
Purify!
The purification won't
make it in time!
Instructor...
Sir Noor, I'm sorry.
I am but a mere soldier.
I chose this path because I admired
the Shield Sovereign Dandalg.
If someone on the verge of danger is
in front of me I want to protect them,
but right now...
It can't be...
Still? In that condition?!
Times like this...
I wish that Noor was still around.
Is that what he meant?
He isn't foolish or anything.
That's exactly the kind of person
I've always looked up to and chased after.
Doing whatever you can to protect someone,
even if it means sacrificing yourself...
A true Shield!
But that man... he's already...
That's good...
I can make this work out after all.
#5 I Parry a Frog